<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-10-24T19:36:50+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Beacon</title><subtitle>The Beacon is Martingrove's newspaper.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">A Message for Students</title><link href="/2020/05/A_Message_for_Students.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Message for Students" /><published>2020-05-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-05-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2020/05/A_Message_for_Students</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/05/A_Message_for_Students.html">&lt;p&gt;So, we aren’t going back to school tomorrow. Whether you are a part of
the &quot;I knew the lockdown would be extended&quot; group, or one of the
hopeful students who wanted their school schedule back, we are in this
together (but 6 feet apart of course.) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This period of self isolation has been a unique experience no one could
have predicted. Some people seem to be enjoying their individual time or
bonding time with family, while others long to be outside, hanging out
with friends and going on adventures. All I can say is, this too, shall
pass. Keep up with your Google Classroom notifications and join the
class calls- I know it can be easy to ignore the notifications, but you
have to remember that you will need this knowledge for years of
education to come. Still, don't be too hard on yourself. If you aren't
being as productive as you were before, it’s because change is
exhausting. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, I must include special mentions to the Class of 2020. Even
though the world is turning upside down, we all had expectations for our
senior year that are just not going to happen. It's unfortunate how we
have been impacted, but the best years of our life are yet to come. So,
hold on to hope and dream for the future because there are great things
to come for all of us. Thanks for reading, fellow quaran-teen! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image Source: &lt;em&gt;“Writing with a Graphic Pen” by Viktor Hanacek from
Picjumbo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ntelesford</name></author><category term="featured" /><summary type="html">So, we aren’t going back to school tomorrow. Whether you are a part of the &quot;I knew the lockdown would be extended&quot; group, or one of the hopeful students who wanted their school schedule back, we are in this together (but 6 feet apart of course.) </summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/2020-05-15-A_Message_for_Students_photo.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Female Representation in Journalism: A Harsh Reality</title><link href="/2020/05/Female_Representation_in_Journalism_-_Sanaa_Mahmud.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Female Representation in Journalism: A Harsh Reality " /><published>2020-05-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-05-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2020/05/Female_Representation_in_Journalism_-_Sanaa_Mahmud</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/05/Female_Representation_in_Journalism_-_Sanaa_Mahmud.html">&lt;p&gt;Imagine you get a job in your dream field of work. You start off well,
yet after a while, you realize that your role in the company is not
advancing and your work is being limited. This is how women in
journalism feel on a daily basis. Despite the major strides made
regarding gender equality, the world of journalism is still very
imbalanced when it comes to the representation of males versus females.
In recent years, studies and data have shown that there are more females
making up journalism students in universities and colleges. Yet, females
only make up 39% of newsrooms. Therefore, the news is predominantly
covered by men. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of this imbalance in representation comes from past and current
gender stereotypes. In 2016, it was reported that in the United States,
fields of reporting with over 50% of female representation included
lifestyle, education, and healthcare. Whereas, there was less that 30%
of female representation in topics such as sports, weather, and crime
and justice. In Canadian newsrooms, many major news organizations have
also shown large gender gaps, according to a 2015 study. &lt;em&gt;The Global
Media Monitoring Project&lt;/em&gt; looked into 23 Canadian news organizations,
including &lt;em&gt;CBC&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CTV&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;the Toronto Star&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;the Globe and Mail&lt;/em&gt;.
They found that only 43% of reporters were female, and that only 31% of
women reporters had covered stories regarding politics and government.
Additionally, the study found that women were more likely than men to
include female sources in their articles. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You must be wondering: Why is equal representation in the news
important? One major reason that gender equality in the media matters is
because women bring new and different perspectives to journalism,
sparking more interest in global news and creating a broader audience.
&lt;em&gt;The Women’s Media Center&lt;/em&gt; put out a study in 2017, outlining the
consequences of a lack of female representation in journalism. The study
stated that in 12 top U.S. news outlets, campus sexual assault stories
were mainly written by men. In these stories, male journalists were more
likely to focus on the impact on the perpetrator, and his behaviour
surrounding rape charges. On the other hand, female journalists who
covered sexual assault were more likely to focus on the victim’s
behaviour, and how rape impacted them. This is just one example
revealing a difference in perspective that occurs when the same type of
story is covered by a man or a woman. Women also emphasize different
ideas than men. A study in 2013 found that women writing editorial
pieces prominently used words including abuse, assault, children,
equality, education, discrimination, and violence. This difference in
subject matter and perspective is important to have in the media,
especially in news and broadcasting. It provides a more detailed and
comprehensive story, helping the audience to become better-informed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, there is one major question left: Is it possible to have equal
representation in newsrooms, and how can we achieve it? Firstly, it is
TOTALLY possible to represent males and females equally in journalism!
The world of reporting, broadcasting, and news would be far better if
there were many contrasting perspectives on world issues. Journalism
could be elevated from what it is now, to keep national and global
audiences engaged and well-informed. To achieve this proper balance, we
can be aware of the challenges that women in journalism face, and stand
up for their right to equal representation and opportunities. We can use
our voices, as well as social media platforms to advocate for this
cause, and inform those around us about the issue. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image Source: &lt;em&gt;“Woman Writing in Notebook” by Ivan Samkov from Pexels&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>smahmud</name></author><category term="featured" /><summary type="html">Imagine you get a job in your dream field of work. You start off well, yet after a while, you realize that your role in the company is not advancing and your work is being limited. This is how women in journalism feel on a daily basis. Despite the major strides made regarding gender equality, the world of journalism is still very imbalanced when it comes to the representation of males versus females. In recent years, studies and data have shown that there are more females making up journalism students in universities and colleges. Yet, females only make up 39% of newsrooms. Therefore, the news is predominantly covered by men. </summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/2020-05-15-Female_Representation_in_Journalism_-_Sanaa_Mahmud_photo.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Knowledge is Power: Why to Stay Informed During the Pandemic</title><link href="/2020/05/Knowledge_is_Power_Why_to_Stay_Informed_During_the_Pandemic_-_Sanaa_Mahmud.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Knowledge is Power: Why to Stay Informed During the Pandemic" /><published>2020-05-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-05-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2020/05/Knowledge_is_Power_Why_to_Stay_Informed_During_the_Pandemic_-_Sanaa_Mahmud</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/05/Knowledge_is_Power_Why_to_Stay_Informed_During_the_Pandemic_-_Sanaa_Mahmud.html">&lt;p&gt;If there is one word to describe the world we live in today, it would
be, “uncertain.” Uncertain of what to do, where to go next, and what is
going to happen in the near future. Everywhere we turn, the words
“virus” and “pandemic” flood our ears, making it incredibly challenging
to think of anything else. It may be tempting to try to block out the
world altogether to avoid bad news, but one thing to remember is that we
must stay informed during these times. We have to stay on top of
information regarding our global situation, for a number of valid
reasons. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For one, keeping updated is a way to do our part to stop the spread of
the virus. We all have an important role to play within our communities.
We have to look out for ourselves, and those around us. You may hear the
phrase, “we’re all in this together” quite often, and wonder what it
means. Obviously we’re not physically together, and isolation makes it
feel like we’re actually farther apart. And no, it’s not a High School
Musical reference. This phrase is meant to convey that everyone is
currently going through the same situation. It means we all need to
remain united against a common threat, and work to keep ourselves and
the community safe. This can be achieved through listening to our public
health officials, and taking proper precautions, like social distancing.
One can only be aware of these precautions by keeping up with the news,
and staying informed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another reason to stay informed is knowing how to respond to challenges
during this time. Most of the world, let alone all MCI students, have
never been part of any pandemic situation before. No one knows how to
act or where to begin trying to cope with all the changes. These changes
cause many to feel scared, helpless and not in control. By staying
informed on new developments of the virus, as well as the necessary
precautions to take, you are educating yourself on how to combat our new
reality. This education becomes a way to feel in control, and stay on
top of the fear. A study conducted by the International Journal of
Environmental Research and Public Health (IJERPH) found that those who
had reliable and updated information regarding the coronavirus felt more
prepared to handle it. Also, people who received accurate information
about the virus had lower levels of stress, anxiety and depression. So
when staying updated on information concerning the virus, not only are
you learning about ways to react, but you are possibly improving the
status of your mental health. By learning more about what threatens us,
we can combat fear, and remain feeling in control. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another major reason to remain informed is to stay connected with the
outside world. Through television, newspapers, and the internet, we are
able to momentarily escape our self-isolation and see what is happening
throughout the globe. For example, by watching the news, not only are
you getting information, you are seeing the contrasting effects of the
virus around the world. You get to see what other people are doing, and
how other countries are reacting. Most importantly, you get to be
reminded that you are not alone, since the whole world is going through
the same thing. Getting information and updates is your ticket to
experiencing the world once again, because it allows you to see what
others are doing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, although our world may seem scary and uncertain, it is also one
that will go down in the history books. People will remember these past
few months as the worst crisis since WWII, meaning we are all making
history. I’d like to believe our children or even grandchildren may ask
about this time; how it felt to live in self-isolation, be off from
school, and watch everything around us shut down. In order to speak to
our experiences, we should be aware of what’s happening throughout the
world. Even though this crisis is terrible, we should be immersing
ourselves in the current information and updates, so we remember when
it’s over. Those who weren’t present during this time will want to know
everything, and I, for one, want to be able to share it. So, think about
it like this: staying informed is a way to truly be a part of this
event, and if we don’t know what’s going on around us, we may be letting
a historic occurrence pass us by. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To conclude, it is really important to remain informed and updated about
the virus, as well as other current events around the world. Now, this
doesn’t mean glueing yourself to the TV or reading every newspaper
article. You can be informed by just watching the news once a day, for a
brief period of time. Alternately, you can go online to the &lt;em&gt;Globe and
Mail&lt;/em&gt;, the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt;, the &lt;em&gt;Washington Post&lt;/em&gt;, or countless other
newspaper sources, and read a couple articles. By taking ten minutes out
of each day, you can learn so much about what is happening around you.
Being informed is all about feeling confident and resilient enough to go
about your daily life, without feeling worried. We must remember that
even in a world of uncertainty, there are ways to fight back, and remain
in control. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sources: &lt;a href=&quot;https://cmha.bc.ca/covid-19-stay-informed/&quot;&gt;https://cmha.bc.ca/covid-19-stay-informed/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mdpi.com/1660-4601/17/5/1729&quot;&gt;https://www.mdpi.com/1660-4601/17/5/1729&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image Source: &lt;em&gt;“The New York Times Newspaper” by cottonbro from Pexels&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>smahmud</name></author><category term="featured" /><summary type="html">If there is one word to describe the world we live in today, it would be, “uncertain.” Uncertain of what to do, where to go next, and what is going to happen in the near future. Everywhere we turn, the words “virus” and “pandemic” flood our ears, making it incredibly challenging to think of anything else. It may be tempting to try to block out the world altogether to avoid bad news, but one thing to remember is that we must stay informed during these times. We have to stay on top of information regarding our global situation, for a number of valid reasons. </summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/2020-05-15-Knowledge_is_Power_Why_to_Stay_Informed_During_the_Pandemic_-_Sanaa_Mahmud_photo.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">So Much for ‘Reconciliation’</title><link href="/2020/05/So_Much_for_Reconciliation_-_Luke_Baumgart.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="So Much for 'Reconciliation'" /><published>2020-05-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-05-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2020/05/So_Much_for_Reconciliation_-_Luke_Baumgart</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/05/So_Much_for_Reconciliation_-_Luke_Baumgart.html">&lt;p&gt;The latest conflict between the Wet’suwet’en Hereditary Chiefs and their
supporters, and those supporting the Coastal GasLink Pipeline has
revealed that Canada remains set in its role as a colonizer. Before the
beginning of this year, it may have been easy to deny that Canada
remains a colonizing power, but no longer can that appeal to ignorance
be made. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those unfamiliar with the situation, here are the main events. At
the beginning of this year, following a Dec. 31st injunction from the
B.C. Supreme Court, militarized RCMP officers raided a camp of First
Nations land defenders, arresting people on their sovereign territory.
In reaction, protesters led demonstrations and blocked railways across
the country. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actions of these protesters and the original Wet'suwet'en land
defenders have been highly criticized across Canada in ways that are
misguided and problematic. The record must be set straight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An RCMP raid on Wet’suwet’en land amounts to an invasion of a foreign
nation. According to the Canadian law and the United Nations Declaration
on the Rights of Indigenous People, these land defenders have the right
to self-governance and territorial sovereignty. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an act of colonial exploitation. Canada is a colonial power.
Canada was created to extract natural resources. To do this, the
Canadian Government along with private corporations killed, ethnically
cleansed, and commited cultural genocide against First Nations people.
We saw this in Residential Schools, in the Sixties Scoop and we continue
to see it today. This was done to free up land for both resource
extraction and settlers to do the work. It is inherently racist and
morally abhorrent in every way. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A common misconception is that the pipeline is legitimate and accepted
because the elected band council system has okayed it. It must be
recognized though, that the elected band council is a system put into
place by the Indian Act to make band councils more similar to other
colonial governments. According to the traditional Wet'suwet'en system
of government, the Hereditary Chiefs are the true and legitimate
leaders. This has been upheld by the Supreme Court.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, putting all this aside, there should be no pipelines. At all.
Anywhere. We are in a climate emergency. Arguments are made about the
economy and the need to slowly ease off fossil fuels. Unfortunately, the
time for that is long gone. Science says we need to stop producing oil
and natural gas now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many Canadians are unaware of these issues, but it has become
increasingly important in political discourse in recent years. Recent
movement towards “Reconciliation” would have the average citizen believe
that Canada and its government have ceased colonial actions and are
working to right the wrongs done over the past 400 years. This most
recent conflict clearly shows that the government cares not for
Indigenous Peoples’ rights when there is money to be made.
Reconciliation is a farce while colonization continues. Knowing this,
when you stand for O Canada, ask yourself: Do you stand for colonialism?
Do you stand for cultural genocide? Do you stand for ignoring human
rights? If not, consider staying seated. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Opinion Piece *&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image source: &lt;em&gt;“Wet'suwet'en Solidarity Event - Rail Yard near Pioneer
Village Station Blockaded - Vaughan, Toronto, Ontario - February 15,
2020.” By &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/salty_soul/49542240712/&quot;&gt;Jason Hargrove from
Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>lbaumgart</name></author><category term="featured" /><summary type="html">The latest conflict between the Wet’suwet’en Hereditary Chiefs and their supporters, and those supporting the Coastal GasLink Pipeline has revealed that Canada remains set in its role as a colonizer. Before the beginning of this year, it may have been easy to deny that Canada remains a colonizing power, but no longer can that appeal to ignorance be made. </summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/2020-05-01-So_Much_for_Reconciliation_-_Luke_Baumgart_photo.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Messages to a Younger Me</title><link href="/2020/04/Messages_to_a_Younger_Me_-_Aaliyah_Aden-Sabriye.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Messages to a Younger Me" /><published>2020-04-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-04-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2020/04/Messages_to_a_Younger_Me_-_Aaliyah_Aden-Sabriye</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/04/Messages_to_a_Younger_Me_-_Aaliyah_Aden-Sabriye.html">&lt;p&gt;i’m sorry &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;sorry i held you captive by refusing to listen&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;sorry i listened to their screams &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;that they were making us stronger &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;when we just needed to be safe—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i was a kid &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i’m sorry i didn’t take care of you as well as i should have&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;sorry i can’t remember much of you &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i’m sorry i still struggle with the insecurities &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;you tried so hard to beat down &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i’m sorry you’re still hurting—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;sorry that the same arms that held you&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;when you were looking for comfort &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;were the very ones &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;that you needed to be shielded from &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i’m sorry you were forced to grow up &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;faster than you should’ve &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;sorry you isolated yourself &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;because you didn’t have anyone else to go to&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i’m sorry you weren’t able to be a kid&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;for very long&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i’m sorry they hurt you&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;sorry they neglected and belittled you—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;as you continued to search for praise&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;for them to lift you up as they tore you down&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i’m sorry their words still hurt you—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;they’re holding you captive &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;with words that mean nothing &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and actions that mean everything &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i’m sorry that sorry isn’t enough&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to give back the childhood that they stole &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image source: &lt;em&gt;“Hand with oil pastel draws the heart”
by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pexels.com/@kaboompics?utm_content=attributionCopyText&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_source=pexels&quot;&gt;Kaboompics.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pexels.com/photo/hand-with-oil-pastel-draws-the-heart-6333/?utm_content=attributionCopyText&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_source=pexels&quot;&gt;[Pexels]{.underline}&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>aaden-sabriye</name></author><category term="featured" /><summary type="html">i’m sorry </summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/2020-04-30-Messages_to_a_Younger_Me_-_Aaliyah_Aden-Sabriye_photo.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Podcast Pontifications</title><link href="/2020/04/Podcast_Pontifications_-_Susanna_Liao.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Podcast Pontifications" /><published>2020-04-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-04-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2020/04/Podcast_Pontifications_-_Susanna_Liao</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/04/Podcast_Pontifications_-_Susanna_Liao.html">&lt;p&gt;You’re on the bus, in a car, in your room, waiting at a doctor’s office,
or just sitting around doing nothing. It’s not worth the effort to pull
out a book, there’s no access to your favourite TV show, and you want
something a bit more rewarding than listening to music. The solutionー
podcasts! Podcasts are one of the most underappreciated forms of media
out there. They are audio programs that focus on the spoken word, like a
radio talk show but better. Podcasts are easily accessible, widely
available, and there is a podcast for everyone out there, whether you’re
looking for lighthearted comedy, news and politics, or dramatic
storytelling. But where to start? In a day and age where time is
literally money and there are thousands of forms of entertainment all
vying for your attention, it can seem overwhelming to decide what to
choose. That’s why I’m here to help! I’ve chosen a couple of my all time
favourite podcasts (and I listen to a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt; of podcasts). So, whether
you’re brand new to the world of podcasts or an experienced veteran,
here are some of my suggestions that I hope each of you will at least
give a try. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Anthropocene Reviewed by John Green&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Anthropocene Reviewed&lt;/em&gt; is a monthly podcast about all things human.
In this podcast, John Green (author of &lt;em&gt;The Fault in Our Stars&lt;/em&gt; among
other things) reviews anything and everything on a five star scale. The
topics range from the QWERTY keyboard to velociraptors to teddy bears to
&lt;em&gt;Super Mario Kart&lt;/em&gt;. On the surface it may seem like a shallow, fun-time,
but it often delves deep into what connects us all and makes us human
through the lens of ridiculous and everyday objects and events. By the
end of an episode about hot dog eating contests you may be having an
existential crisis about the worth of your own existence and why we’re
all really here. Sometimes heartbreaking and sometimes uplifting, every
episode is a new and delightful discovery about what it means to be
human. Episodes are about half an hour long and there’s no set order or
plot, so you can pick it up anywhere, but you may find yourself binge
listening like I do. It’s one of my all time favourite podcasts because
I love the juxtaposition of absurd topics and thoughtful discussion.
It’ll make you laugh one moment and cry the next, which is why I
recommend &lt;em&gt;The Anthropocene Reviewed&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Myths and Legends by Jason and Carissa Weiser&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Myths and Legends&lt;/em&gt; is a weekly podcast retelling old musty myths in a
new, funky way. This podcast aims to tell stories, from (in)famous tales
like &lt;em&gt;Robin Hood&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Hansel and Gretel&lt;/em&gt; to ones you may have never
heard of but will love, like &lt;em&gt;The Eyrie and Meng Jiangnu and the Great
Wall&lt;/em&gt;. It also features a “Creature of the Week” segment, discussing
foolish and fantastical creatures from myths all over the world. Jason
Weiser recounts these tales in a way that’s entertaining, funny, and
keeps you on the edge of your seat. This podcast is an old favourite of
mine because it’s lighthearted and comforting, like a good chicken
noodle soup. &lt;em&gt;Myths and Legends&lt;/em&gt; is something that I go back to time and
again because it’s casual enough to listen to while doing chores or
other mind numbing tasks, funny and entertaining, but still carry a
lesson. Episodes are usually half an hour to an hour long; some stories
split into sagas several episodes long, but most are individual
installments you can pick and choose from. I’d recommend &lt;em&gt;Myths and
Legends&lt;/em&gt; to anyone looking for an interesting and educational
storytelling podcast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Science Vs by Gimlet Media&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Science Vs&lt;/em&gt; is a weekly podcast that examines controversial topics in a
science focused way. Narrated by Wendy Zuckerman and produced by Gimlet
Media, this podcast covers many topics, from police shootings to killer
asteroids to the coronavirus to vaping. It’s a great surface level
introduction to these topics and many more, debating the pros and cons
and often bringing in experts to talk about them. &lt;em&gt;Science Vs&lt;/em&gt; is both
educational and entertaining to listen to, and the topics are often very
relevant to current events or everyday life. I like the informational
yet conversational tone of the podcast and that it gives a generic idea
of the topic without going too in depth, so it can be informative
without feeling stuffy and formal. Episodes are about an hour long and
stand alone, so you can listen to just what piques your interest without
being dragged down by over a hundred episodes. I’d recommend &lt;em&gt;Science
Vs&lt;/em&gt; to anyone interested in learning something new in a fun and engaging
way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I encourage you to go explore podcasts on Spotify, Soundcloud, or any
other digital platform. Happy podcasting! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image sources:&lt;em&gt;“Anthropocene Reviewed” from
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.johngreenbooks.com/&quot;&gt;johngreenbooks.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Science Vs” from &lt;a href=&quot;https://gimletmedia.com/&quot;&gt;gimletmedia.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Myths and Legends” from
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mythpodcast.com/&quot;&gt;mythpodcast.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>sliao</name></author><category term="featured" /><summary type="html">You’re on the bus, in a car, in your room, waiting at a doctor’s office, or just sitting around doing nothing. It’s not worth the effort to pull out a book, there’s no access to your favourite TV show, and you want something a bit more rewarding than listening to music. The solutionー podcasts! Podcasts are one of the most underappreciated forms of media out there. They are audio programs that focus on the spoken word, like a radio talk show but better. Podcasts are easily accessible, widely available, and there is a podcast for everyone out there, whether you’re looking for lighthearted comedy, news and politics, or dramatic storytelling. But where to start? In a day and age where time is literally money and there are thousands of forms of entertainment all vying for your attention, it can seem overwhelming to decide what to choose. That’s why I’m here to help! I’ve chosen a couple of my all time favourite podcasts (and I listen to a lot of podcasts). So, whether you’re brand new to the world of podcasts or an experienced veteran, here are some of my suggestions that I hope each of you will at least give a try. Enjoy!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/2020-04-30-Podcast_Pontifications_-_Susanna_Liao_photo.PNG" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Moral Dilemma of COVID-19</title><link href="/2020/04/The_Moral_Dilemma_of_COVID-19_-_Maya_Hutzul.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Moral Dilemma of COVID-19" /><published>2020-04-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-04-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2020/04/The_Moral_Dilemma_of_COVID-19_-_Maya_Hutzul</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/04/The_Moral_Dilemma_of_COVID-19_-_Maya_Hutzul.html">&lt;p&gt;COVID-19 is spreading quickly - so quickly, in fact, that by the time
this article is released, these statistics will already be out of
date*. When news of the virus reached the international community, the
majority of the coverage was focused on China, particularly on the
millions under quarantine in the province of Hubei. However, by the end
of February, there was news of outbreaks in South Korea, Italy, and
Iran. By mid-March, the majority of the world was under quarantine as
outbreaks spread across the world. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;COVID-19 has been spreading rapidly around the world, with over one
million cases and 56,000 confirmed deaths. Canada currently has 12,000
confirmed cases and over 170 deaths. The United States, however, has
quickly become an epicenter for the virus, with over 265,000 cases and
6,700 deaths. An online polling survey by Leger suggests that Americans
aren't taking isolation as seriously as Canadians - only 86% of US
respondents were adhering to the required 2 metre distance rules, in
comparison to 95% of Canadians. Although this number might seem small,
it could be a significant factor in determining the death tolls in both
countries. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disinformation is still prominent in the battle against COVID-19, and
undermines public attempts to fight it. From online posts claiming that
lemons ward off the virus, to Fox News anchors saying that holding your
breath for more than ten seconds will prevent it, disinformation is
widespread. Worse still, people’s attempts to try to make a profit off
of selling their own home remedies do more than damage their personal
credibility - they can prevent individuals, who have the disease, from
getting life-saving treatment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While choosing not to spread disinformation might be an easy choice,
what the governments of the world are faced with today is far from easy.
As the world goes into quarantine in an attempt to contain the spread of
the virus, economic activity halts. This poses many problems, and it is
inevitable that massive job losses follow.  In a one week period this
March, the government of Canada received nearly 500,000 applications for
unemployment insurance, an amount only matched by an &lt;em&gt;eight&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;month&lt;/em&gt;
period during the recession in 2009. This presents a moral dilemma - a
choice between people’s lives, and their livelihoods. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The governments of the world, as this crisis continues to unfold, will
have to tread carefully. Are they prepared to deal with a potential
depression, and the mental health issues and business failures that
would result from it? There are no easy answers, and this is not an easy
situation. All we can do is stay safe as best we can, and practise
social distancing for the good of our country and the world. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;* &lt;em&gt;This article was originally released on April 3rd, 2020.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image source: &lt;em&gt;“Concept of Covid-19 In Red Background” by Edward Jenner
from Pexels.com&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mhutzul</name></author><category term="featured" /><summary type="html">COVID-19 is spreading quickly - so quickly, in fact, that by the time this article is released, these statistics will already be out of date*. When news of the virus reached the international community, the majority of the coverage was focused on China, particularly on the millions under quarantine in the province of Hubei. However, by the end of February, there was news of outbreaks in South Korea, Italy, and Iran. By mid-March, the majority of the world was under quarantine as outbreaks spread across the world. </summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/2020-04-30-The_Moral_Dilemma_of_COVID-19_-_Maya_Hutzul_photo.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Unlocking Your Full Potential</title><link href="/2020/04/Unlocking_Your_Full_Potential_-_Emily_Kim.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unlocking Your Full Potential" /><published>2020-04-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-04-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2020/04/Unlocking_Your_Full_Potential_-_Emily_Kim</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/04/Unlocking_Your_Full_Potential_-_Emily_Kim.html">&lt;p&gt;Recently, I picked up the book &lt;em&gt;Mindset&lt;/em&gt; by Carol Dweck and became
obsessed. While I run the risk of being melodramatic, I must say that
this book has offered me a new perspective on life and a solution to a
problem that I once thought unsolvable. Now, before I go into any
further details, I want to ask you, the reader, a question. Do you think
that intelligence is something you are born with or something you can
develop?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Before reading this book I always believed that intelligence, among
other attributes, was a fixed value that couldn’t be altered. I believed
that while hard work could allow you to accomplish more, it wouldn’t
change your inherent aptitude for something. For example, when I would
do poorly on a math or science test (and trust me this happened far too
often), I would tell myself that “science just wasn’t my thing.” The
problem with this mentality is that it didn't allow room for growth. In
my head, it felt irrational and too challenging to constantly put more
effort into science. Sure, I could study a week in advance for every
science test, but what was the point? I didn’t want to keep putting my
blood, sweat and tears into science just to stay on par with the rest of
my marks, or peers (who I believed had natural aptitudes for science).
What I didn’t understand though, is that nobody can sustainably excel at
something without putting work in. Intelligence and skills can be
cultivated in almost every facet of your life. Personality,
intelligence, athletic ability, social skills etc. can all be developed,
over time, through hard work, good strategies and input from others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; By viewing our attributes, and others', as fixed values, we are forced
to place our self-esteem on our natural abilities alone. So, when faced
with failure, we are devastated as we believe that we will never
overcome them fully. Conversely, with a growth mindset, you spend less
time worrying about how talented or &quot;good&quot; at something you are and
focus instead on learning and growing your abilities. Often, when faced
with criticism or failure, we retract into feelings of insecurity and
defensiveness, which directly inhibits our growth and opportunity to
learn from our mistakes. People are born with an inherent love for
learning, but a fixed mindset, derived from society's institutionalized
habit of praising natural ability, ruins this. We live in a world where
we believe people are either innately superior or inferior and,
therefore, we stick to easy tasks that we excel in, to repeatedly affirm
our feelings of superiority, while simultaneously avoiding things that
expose our inferiority. We sweep under the rug, the parts of our life
that need the most nurturing and attention, leaving them more neglected
and weak than ever before. With this behaviour, we slam the door on any
chance of genuine improvement and growth by letting our conquerable
weaknesses constantly hold us back from our true potential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this new year, I urge you to reignite your passion for learning by
letting go of your fear of failure through the belief that skills and
ability can be grown and cultivated. Unfortunately, I can't get into
all the nitty-gritty details about what a growth mindset is and how to
achieve it (it’ll take up the entire Beacon), so I strongly urge you to
read Dr. Dweck's book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s important to note though that real change and improvement will take
commitment and patience. You can’t expect to immediately flourish at
something you are weak in, just by suddenly putting more effort in. It
will take dedication and time to hone your skills and help them develop
to the standard at which you want them. The main idea is to not get
discouraged. When I first took on this mindset, believe it or not, I
performed worse than I usually do. But instead of giving up, I pressed
on and used my low marks to determine my mistakes and how to better
prepare in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are reading this and somehow haven’t gotten bored from my
rambling, I sincerely hope that you are motivated and interested in
taking up this new attitude and perspective on life. Our world needs
more growth-minded people than ever before, as we live in a world with
infinite possibilities and challenges that can only be overcome by those
most willing to try. As I wrap this up, I'll leave you with one last
piece of advice: NEVER - especially in the face of adversity - fixate on
your present ability, but instead on your potential, what is possible
and what you can become.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image Source:
&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/128573122@N05/18658685910&quot;&gt;&quot;Mindset&quot;&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/128573122@N05&quot;&gt;davis.steve32&lt;/a&gt; is
licensed under &lt;a href=&quot;https://search.creativecommons.org/photos/null?ref=ccsearch&amp;amp;atype=rich&quot;&gt;CC BY
2.0 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ekim</name></author><category term="featured" /><summary type="html">Recently, I picked up the book Mindset by Carol Dweck and became obsessed. While I run the risk of being melodramatic, I must say that this book has offered me a new perspective on life and a solution to a problem that I once thought unsolvable. Now, before I go into any further details, I want to ask you, the reader, a question. Do you think that intelligence is something you are born with or something you can develop?</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/2020-04-30-Unlocking_Your_Full_Potential_-_Emily_Kim_photo.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">MEC Environmental Column: How Bears Can Celebrate Earth Hour</title><link href="/2020/04/MEC_Environmental_Column_How_Bears_Can_Celebrate_Earth_Hour_-_Linda_Li-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MEC Environmental Column: How Bears Can Celebrate Earth Hour" /><published>2020-04-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-04-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2020/04/MEC_Environmental_Column_How_Bears_Can_Celebrate_Earth_Hour_-_Linda_Li-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/04/MEC_Environmental_Column_How_Bears_Can_Celebrate_Earth_Hour_-_Linda_Li-2.html">&lt;p&gt;Hey Bears! Earth Hour 2020 (&lt;strong&gt;Saturday March 28th, 2020, at 8:30 pm&lt;/strong&gt;)
is rapidly approaching. You probably already know what Earth Hour is,
and you might think that it’s somewhat silly. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nobody actually believes that a bunch of people turning off some
lights for one hour is going to change anything, do they? And our school
can’t really participate anyway. The timing doesn’t allow it and if we
turn off our lights, the school will be plunged into darkness.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indeed, it is an unfortunate truth that MCI’s notorious lack of windows
and natural lighting makes it difficult for us to celebrate Earth Hour.
And yes, we obviously can’t “properly” participate because there’s no
school on the 28th. There won’t ever be school during Earth Hour, since
it takes place in the evening and on the last Saturday of March.
Regardless, MCI and many other schools do their bit on the Friday
before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the question still remains - does Earth Hour make a difference?
According to the mission statement of EarthHour.org, (the official
website for… well, Earth Hour), the main purpose of Earth Hour is to
make a symbolic commitment to the betterment of our environment. The
event is meant to “spark global conversations on protecting nature not
only to combat the climate crisis, but to ensure our own health,
happiness, prosperity and even survival.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The carbon emission reduction of the event is indeed negligible (Gollom,
2014), but millions of people across 180 countries participate in Earth
Hour every year, meaning they have taken the time out of their day to
consider how they as individuals can impact the planet. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, Earth Hour is simplistic. Anyone can do it and the second it’s
over, we can continue on with our wasteful, energy-guzzling, consumer
lifestyles. But for that brief hour, people are acting in unity for our
environment. Any act of positive unity in our increasingly more
complicated society is a moment to be cherished. So if you can, please
do consider participating in Earth Hour 2020 with your families and
conserve energy whenever possible to carry on the spirit of
environmental stewardship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Energy conservation tips include: turning off lights that are not in
use, unplugging appliances that are not in use (yeah it’s annoying to
plug them in again, but come on! That’s a first world problem if I ever
heard one) and changing to energy efficient lights and appliances (this
tip does depend on how cool your parents are, of course). The internet
is at your fingertips for more information on how you can make a
difference, of course. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy Earth Hour, MCI!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image Source: &lt;em&gt;NASA Earth Observatory/Joshua Stevens; NOAA National
Environmental Satellite, Data, and Information Service.&lt;/em&gt;
ervice.*
rvice.*&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>lli</name></author><summary type="html">Hey Bears! Earth Hour 2020 (Saturday March 28th, 2020, at 8:30 pm) is rapidly approaching. You probably already know what Earth Hour is, and you might think that it’s somewhat silly. </summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/2020-04-04-MEC_Environmental_Column_How_Bears_Can_Celebrate_Earth_Hour_-_Linda_Li-2_photo.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">A Year in Review: Ranking My Top 10 Films of 2019</title><link href="/2020/02/File.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Year in Review: Ranking My Top 10 Films of 2019" /><published>2020-02-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-02-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2020/02/File</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/02/File.html">&lt;p&gt;Over the past twelve months, we were handed a diverse collection of
films. Be it comedies, thrillers, action movies, or dramas, filmmakers
new and old raised the bar for this medium in 2019. As the year comes to
an end, I am taking a look back and ranking my top ten movies of the
year. I chose the films that challenged me as a viewer, made me think
for days after I watched it, and most importantly, films that were just
really fun to watch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10. &lt;strong&gt;Climax&lt;/strong&gt; Dir. Gasper Noé &lt;em&gt;Climax&lt;/em&gt; follows a group of aspiring
dancers in an abandoned school, as their rehearsal spirals out of
control into madness. This film is a visually stunning, yet disturbing
erotic rush from start to finish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9. &lt;strong&gt;Shazam!&lt;/strong&gt; Dir. David F. Sandberg From DC Comics, &lt;em&gt;Shazam&lt;/em&gt;! follows
14-year-old Billy Batson as he must learn how to deal with God-like
superpowers. With family values at the core of this film and a stellar
child cast, Shazam! is the most heartwarming superhero film of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8. &lt;strong&gt;Ad Astra&lt;/strong&gt; Dir. James Gray Brad Pitt soars in this film which
explores the powerful bond between a father and son. Cinematographer
Hoyte van Hoytema delivers a visual spectacle of outer space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7. &lt;strong&gt;The Peanut Butter Falcon&lt;/strong&gt; Dir. Tyler Nilson, Michael Schwartz A
young man with down syndrome escapes his nursing facility with dreams of
attending a wrestling school. Shia LaBeouf is mesmerizing in this
charming homage to a Mark Twain classic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6. &lt;strong&gt;Midsommar&lt;/strong&gt; Dir. Ari Aster &lt;em&gt;Midsommar&lt;/em&gt; is a confusing, thought
provoking, and ambitious film. Director Ari Aster creates another
masterfully crafted horror film that almost rivals Aster’s previous
classic, Hereditary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5. &lt;strong&gt;The Lighthouse&lt;/strong&gt; Dir. Robert Eggers Robert Pattinson and Willem
Dafoe give strong performances in this wicked tale of two lighthouse
keepers on a distant island in New England. Robert Eggers really
solidifies himself as a strong filmmaker in the horror genre with this
film.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4. &lt;strong&gt;Rocketman&lt;/strong&gt; Dir. Dexter Fletcher Taron Egerton gives his best
performance yet with &lt;em&gt;Rocketman&lt;/em&gt;. I think it's going to be a long long
time until another film succeeds in creating a movie musical biopic as
intense as &lt;em&gt;Rocketman&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3. &lt;strong&gt;Booksmart&lt;/strong&gt; Dir. Olivia Wilde Olivia Wilde’s directorial debut is a
coming-of-age comedy between two best friends and academic
‘overachievers’ who realize that they’ve wasted their high school years
slaving away instead of having fun. &lt;em&gt;Booksmart&lt;/em&gt; is a wild and fast-paced
movie that is clever in its portrayal of teenagers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2. &lt;strong&gt;Joker&lt;/strong&gt; Dir. Todd Phillips &lt;em&gt;Joker&lt;/em&gt; is a heartbreaking and brutal
take on the clown prince of crime’s origin story. Todd Phillips draws
heavy inspiration from films such as Taxi Driver and The King of Comedy
to construct his tale of a man disregarded by society. Phillips’s Gotham
is corrupt and crime ridden, but it’s the realism that helps amplify the
film’s critique of a society that dismisses its citizens. Joaquin
Phoenix gives a disturbing performance as Arthur Fleck that at times may
call on the viewer to sympathize with him but strictly acknowledges his
vile actions. Todd Phillip’s direction and Lawrence Sher’s beautiful
cinematography accompanied by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/search?rlz=1C1CHBF_enCA725CA725&amp;amp;sxsrf=ACYBGNQuXgS18sMnW0dR0f5xf7FY-3OGsg:1573864416354&amp;amp;q=Hildur+Gu%C3%B0nad%C3%B3ttir&amp;amp;stick=H4sIAAAAAAAAAONgVuLSz9U3MKoyTMvIe8Toyi3w8sc9YSmbSWtOXmM04-IKzsgvd80rySypFNLgYoOy5Lj4pJC0aTBI8XAh8XkWsYp4ZOaklBYpuJce3pCXmHJ4c0lJZhEAfHynQG0AAAA&quot;&gt;Hildur
Guðnadóttir&lt;/a&gt;’s
hypnotizing score help make &lt;em&gt;Joker&lt;/em&gt; standout film from 2019 that must be
viewed more than once to fully grasp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;Parasite&lt;/strong&gt; Dir. Bong Joon-ho Bong Joon-ho’s &lt;em&gt;Parasite&lt;/em&gt; is
undoubtedly 2019’s must see film. Every aspect of this film from its
cast to its cinematography is fantastic. &lt;em&gt;Parasite&lt;/em&gt;’s depiction of
themes of class, wealth, and dignity are apparent but not in your face.
Joon-ho’s slow yet persistent race to the end will keep you on the edge
of your seat. &lt;em&gt;Parasite&lt;/em&gt; follows the extremely poor Kim family as they
launch an all-out assault on the blatantly wealthy Park family. When
Kim’s son, Ki-Woo, secures a job as a tutor for the daughter of the Park
family, he opens the door for the rest of his family to infiltrate the
Park’s home. The Kim family makes quick work of ridding the Park
family’s employees and securing their jobs through tactical and cunning
plans. Each member of the Kim family has a moment to shine. The film
starts off presenting itself as a satirical comedy but takes a jarring
turn into brutality. The film spirals out of control in front of your
eyes and you are forced to view every disturbing second of it. Bong’s
mastery of the camera and formulation of violence is electrifying in
&lt;em&gt;Parasite&lt;/em&gt;. This film is truly an unforgettable piece of cinema will be
deconstructed, examined, and celebrated for years to come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image Source: &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/50048137@N00/8442936606&quot;&gt;&quot;Welcome To The
Theater&quot;&lt;/a&gt; by
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/50048137@N00&quot;&gt;rsmithing&lt;/a&gt; is licensed
under &lt;a href=&quot;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/2.0/?ref=ccsearch&amp;amp;atype=rich&quot;&gt;CC BY-NC 2.0
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ifuse-katayama</name></author><summary type="html">Over the past twelve months, we were handed a diverse collection of films. Be it comedies, thrillers, action movies, or dramas, filmmakers new and old raised the bar for this medium in 2019. As the year comes to an end, I am taking a look back and ranking my top ten movies of the year. I chose the films that challenged me as a viewer, made me think for days after I watched it, and most importantly, films that were just really fun to watch.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/2020-02-01-File_photo.jpg" /></entry></feed>